Md Faisal Hossain



mdfaisal521@outlook.com



01814366774



linkedin.com/in/md-faisal-878628202



https://faisal413.github.io/profile/

Summary

Hi! I am a Software Engineer & I am from Bangladesh. I am 15 years old. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python (programming Language), C# (Programming Language), HTML(Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), JavaScript, Bootstrap(framework), .NET (framework), Unity (game engine), Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator & Microsoft office.

Experience



Game Developer

Unity Technologies

Dec 2020 - Present (4 months +)

Created core game features, including storylines, role-play mechanics and character biographies for new video game or game franchise.

Established documents outlining concept, art, deliverable specifications, game flow charts and overall content to help keep projects moving and teams working together cohesively.

Worked closely with other business analysts, development teams and infrastructure specialists to deliver high availability solutions for missioncritical applications.

Youtube Content Creator

YouTube

Dec 2020 - Present (4 months +)

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCiZs4UiTs3H0IyRTEVNau3g

- · Strengthened content through proofreading and editing.
- Utilized WordPress to upload content, images and pages.
- Rewrote and reorganized site content to better position products and services.
- Develop original content through social listening and independent sources.

Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department of UK

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

- Evaluated source documents to locate information needed for each data entry field.
- · Maintained databases, mailing lists, telephone networks, and other information to facilitate functioning of health education programs.
- · Compiled budget reports, financial spreadsheets and organizational charts to support business operations and improve office organization.

Education

Adarsha Pre-Cadet School

SSC

2020 - 2022

- Minored in Programme
- · Continuing education in science
- Professional development completed in science
- · Majored in science

Skills

C#(Programming Language) • Python (Programming Language) • Unity(game engine) • Video Editing • Logo Design • Audio Editing • JavaScript • Html • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Adobe Photoshop